ALLEN: 8 YEARS OLD
LATE DECEMBER
How scrumptious. What sort of meat is in this?
Horned rabbit meat. Allen hunted them!
Oh? I'd expect nothing less from Rodin's son.
Speaking of, I hear that Krena Village has
successfully met their quota of 20 great boars.
That's great news.
No surprise. I never doubted Dad for a second.
Then why haven't we had any for dinner this year?
Great boar used to be a highlight
of our winter meals.
Good point. Did they all get sent
to the royal capital?
The King was the one who ordered
we hunt more, after all.
Don't be selfish, son.
Sorry...
Harsh!
It's crazy to think serfs eat more meat
than the son of a noble.
Still, it's unfortunate we don't have
any boar meat to serve.
It will put a damper
on the new year's festivities.
Yes, well, there's not much we can do.
Hey, Allen?
Yes?
Hunt a white deer next time, would you?
Elder brother! You have to go through me
to give Allen orders!
What is she, my talent agent?
Thomas, you silly boy.
That's a tall order for Allen.
Very well.
I shall hunt you a white deer.
Hooray!
White deer, eh? Pretty sure it's
a C-rank monster just like the boars.
And I love me a challenge!
EPISODE 8: HUNTSMAN
Did you find what I asked you to?
Bingo!
I've seen them from a distance before,
but white deer are huge up close.
Hopper squad, you're up!
Use Provoke!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Okay, return!
Now!
Hopper squad, do it again!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Return!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit.
Nailed it!
The key to being a Summoner
is knowing how to abuse your summons!
Now, meet your maker!
M-monster at the gates!
Wh-what the heck?
How did it even get in here?!
Take me to...
Master Thomas...
The monster can talk?!
Ugh, this weighs a ton!
I went hunting for Master Thomas.
This white deer is for him.
M-my goodness!
Wow, a white deer!
Amazing...
Look, Mother! Now we have something special
to serve at the new year's party!
Yes, I suppose we do.
Thank you, Allen!
You're most welcome.
This oversized pain in the butt totally
isn't worth the 2,500 EXP that it gives.
I'm never hunting one again!
Tell me, Sebas. Are we certain he has no talent?
Because I don't understand how an eight year old
can hunt C-rank monsters like this.
You must reinvestigate immediately.
Yessir.
Huntsman?
That's right. In light of
your recent accomplishments,
we've decided to assign you a new position.
The huntsman has two duties:
First, hunting monsters
to provide food for the family.
And second, rescuing townsfolk
from any monster attacks.
Basically, a hunter employed by the baron.
Wow.
So, like, I can just go hunting for monsters
every day and call it work?
Of course, we don't expect you to do it for free.
You will receive 100 silver coins,
which is double your current monthly wage.
I see.
They'd rather give me a fixed salary instead
of paying per monster like they did before.
Since a white deer is definitely worth
more than 100 silver coins.
Hm? Not to your liking?
No! It sounds great!
This is the best deal I could ask for!
All I have to do is hunt enough monsters
to provide the necessary meat,
then I'm free to spend
the rest of my time farming goblins!
Man! I'm practically drooling at the thought!
I understand. I'll gladly take on
the title of huntsman.
I'll get started tomorrow...
Hold it. Nobody said you would work every day.
Huh?
Naturally, you must also continue
being Lady Cecil's manservant.
Not to mention your waiter duties. You will only
need to work as a huntsman once a week or so.
Okay...
Your feelings are always written on your face.
I can just shelve this whole idea
if you find it so upsetting.
N-no, sir!
I shall humbly carry out all my duties.
Aw crap! I shouldn't look
a gift horse in the mouth!
MARCH OF THE NEW YEAR
That's his ship!
It's quite a sight to behold up close.
I get that it's powered by magic stones,
but what exactly makes it float?
Don't let it slip that I baked him cookies, okay?
I want him to be surprised!
But of course, milady.
Elder Brother!
Hey, Cecil!
Welcome back, Mihai!
How have you been?
I've been great! Except for how much I missed you!
So, is that good or bad?
You broke your promise to come visit
during summer vacation.
You're right. I'm sorry.
Well, they seem to get along well.
Given that he started attending the Academy
last year, he must be turning 14 soon.
But he looks older than that.
Allow me to take your luggage, milord.
You must be one of the newer servants.
Yes. I have been serving
the family since last fall.
My name is Allen.
He's doing double duty as manservant and huntsman!
Wow! At such a young age?
I can tell you must be very gifted, Allen!
Not at all. I owe it
to Lady Cecil's gracious favor.
He's clearly the mature one of the bunch.
Oh, right.
Here. A souvenir from the capital.
Wow! Thank you!
I'll treasure it forever!
C'mon! Let's go home so you can regale me
with stories of your time at the Academy!
There are yummy cookies waiting for us!
Oh? That sounds wonderful.
I hope Mash and Myulla are doing okay back home.
Gotcha!
Nice. That fills my quota.
Time to pack it in for the day.
Shucks, Allen!
Another big haul today!
Wow.
You even got the big toad I asked for!
Of course, Head Chef!
This will put a smile
on Master Mihai's face for sure.
Guess what, Allen? Master Mihai and Sir Zenoff
are actually having a duel right now!
Wow! This is the first time I've seen
Sir Zenoff using his sword.
Mihai's really holding his own against him.
Let's leave it at that.
Your skills have become much sharper
in the past year, young lad.
Thank you.
Though I think I've outgrown
being called a "young lad."
Oh, Allen. You're back?
That's quite the haul.
Impressive, Allen!
Since you're so tough,
I'd love to spar with you for a bit.
Huh? Are you sure?
Here, Allen.
Thank you, sir.
A mithril sword! Badass!
Man, I haven't sparred with
anybody since I parted ways with Krena.
NAME:
AGE:
TALENT:
LEVEL:
INTELLIGENCE:
LUCK:
HP:
MP:
ATTACK:
ENDURANCE:
AGILITY:
ALLEN
SUMMONER
600 +40
415 +200
412 +130
30 +200
220 +130
220 +20
415 +60
My stats are specced out for hunting right now.
SKILLS:
SUMMON (4), CREATE (4),
FUSE (4) ENHANCE (4),
EXPANSION (3), STORAGE, DELETE
SWORD MASTERY (3), THROW (3)
EXP:
SKILL LEVELS
SUMMON: 4
CREATE: 4
EXP
FUSE: 4
ENHANCE: 4
EXP
But since I started hunting monsters once a week,
SUMMONS AVAILABLE FOR CREATION:
INSECTS: EFGH
BEASTS: EFGH
BIRDS: EFG
PLANTS: EF
STONES: E
I've managed to go from level 13 to 20.
INVENTORY:
INSECTS F 2 COPIES E 1 COPY
BEASTS E 13 COPIES
BIRDS E 4 COPIES
PLANT E 20 COPIES
I bet I can win!
At the ready.
Begin!
Hafta be careful not to hurt him.
Here I come!
Um, he hits like a truck. Seems kinda OP.
Fine! Let me bust out my speed on him.
Wait, he's faster than me, too?!
That feel when you get parried like a total scrub.
Mihai...
Have no fear, my lady.
Huh?
Master Mihai has spent a whole year undergoing
training in the renowned Academy City.
There is no chance he loses
to someone without that experience.
I admit defeat.
Wow!
So cool!
I can certainly see how you made
manservant at your age!
Thank you... milord.
He's in a whole different league!
I never stood a chance.
Amazing, Elder Brother!
I'll give you some credit, Allen.
You weren't half-bad, either.
Why, thank you.
Who died and made you Queen?!
You're so much stronger than you were last year.
Well, that's because I cleared
a dungeon over the summer.
Dungeon?
It's like a maze where you fight monsters.
I needed to clear it
or I would've gotten expelled.
Really?! No wonder you couldn't
come home over the summer.
Clearing a dungeon
for summer homework? That's sick!
Life at the Academy is rough, but it's worth it.
For example, I had the opportunity
to learn the intricacies of swordsmanship
from Dverg the Sword Lord.
Wow, from Lord Dverg himself?!
Neat. Sounds like a stacked teaching staff.
That's amazing! What was he like?
Hm, how can I put it...
Now I get it. He trained
with Sword Lords and cleared dungeons.
Plus, being on normal mode
means that he progresses 100 times faster
than I do on Hell Mode.
So this is how strong
someone with a talent can get
by dedicating a whole year to leveling up, huh?
Tell me, Mihai! When will you come visit us again?
Not until summer of next year, most likely.
Boo...
Please spar with me again when you do!
Sure thing.
But take good care of my sister
while I'm away, would you?
Sound good, Allen?
Uh, yeah.
Screw that.
I'm trying to rise the servant ranks
and make a name for myself.
If I had my way, I'd be out hunting every day!
I'm doomed to serve Cecil forever at this rate!
I gotta figure out a way to quit this gig
without shaming my dad in the process...
A few days later,
Mihai left to return to Academy City.
That's where Krena, Dogora,
and eventually Cecil will go.
Dungeons sound fun. Wish I could clear one.
I'm not crying and these are not tears, got it?!
Uh, sure.
THE HARDCORE GAMER DOMINATES
IN ANOTHER WORLD WITH GARBAGE BALANCING
ALLEN: AGE 8
EARLY APRIL
It's an honor to have you, Viscount Carnel.
Think nothing of it, Baron Granvelle!
Sometimes it can be nice to enjoy
the quaint landscapes of the lifeless backcountry.
Oh really. How wonderful.
Rickel was explaining to me earlier...
Viscount Carnel?
He's in charge of the neighboring fiefdom,
on the other side of the White Dragon Mountains.
The viscount is one rank higher
in social status over the baron.
Why the sudden visit?
Does he have important business here?
Dunno. But I heard he took a magic ship all
the way from the royal capital just to drop by.
Better watch out.
The Granvelles and the Carnels have been
at each other's throats for centuries.
Superb!
This must be the boar meat
I've heard so much about!
Indeed it is. Right, Allen?
Y-yessir.
He knows full well it's just horned rabbit.
Don't want to waste any boar meat
on this joker, huh?
I see. No wonder you wanted
to keep this tasty morsel a secret!
It was by no means a secret.
Man, he's really pissed. But it's only fair.
That scoundrel!
Calling attention to the boar hunts
while we're in front of the King!
This jerk is the one who
spilled the beans to the King
and caused a fuss over the boar meat quota.
Now it all has to go to the royal capital.
I'd like a second serving.
Right away, sir.
Your fiefdom is already better off.
Stop punching down, asshole.
HISTORY LESSONS
WITH RICKEL
History Lessons with Rickel!
Let's get started.
CARNEL FIEFDOM
GRANVELLE FIEFDOM
WHITE DRAGON MOUNTAINS
The White Dragon Mountains
are filled with mithril deposits.
There are multiple mines in both territories,
but because the white dragon
has made its nest on this side,
we can't access any of ours.
That's why the Granvelle Fiefdom
is going through an economic downturn, huh?
Thankfully, the white dragon is pretty fickle,
so it switches to roost on the other side
every hundred years.
Hence, about a century ago, it was the
Carnel Fiefdom that was struggling instead.
I see!
Not an easy problem to solve.
Back then, the Granvelle Fiefdom
might have been the bully.
So, what brings you here today?
I can't imagine you came all this way
just to eat boar meat.
Ah, yes. Of course.
The boar meat was so tasty that I almost forgot.
That's horned rabbit, my dude.
A few days ago, my youngest daughter
underwent the Appraisal Ceremony.
I came here to share the results.
Oh, it's already that time of year?
I really hope Mash has a talent.
He was good with a spear.
TALENT: SPEAR USER
Well, let's hear it.
Fortunately, she's talentless!
Huh? Their reactions don't make sense to me.
It's such a shame, Baron Granvelle.
Two of your three kids got saddled with a talent.
I seem to recall your eldest son
also had a talent, Viscount!
You know how it goes.
We must fulfill the noble's duty.
How is having a talent a bad thing?
Why come all this way on a ship
just to rub that in his face?
The commoners and serfs who I know
were all overjoyed to have a talent.
Is there some kind of downside to it for nobles?
Such tasty boar, simply ham-tacular.
What is this "noble's duty"
they were talking about?
Gotta say, being a noble seems like it sucks.
ALLEN: AGE 9
EARLY OCTOBER
ALLEN'S DAY OFF
So, you've got the day off?
Yeah. I'm actually considering doing my hunting
a little farther away from town.
So I was wondering if you would share your
knowledge about C-rank monsters with me.
I've taken down roughly
10,000 goblins at this point.
There's hardly any left to hunt around here.
NAME:       ALLEN
AGE:
TALENT:
LEVEL:
HP:
MP:
ATTACK:
ENDURANCE:
AGILITY:
INTELLIGENCE:
LUCK:
EXP:
I've leveled up enough
that farming D-rank monsters won't cut it anymore.
SKILLS     SUMMON: 4
CREATE: 4    EXP
FUSE: 4      EXP
ENHANCE: 5    EXP
EXPANSION 3
STORAGE
DELETE
SWORD MASTERY (3)
THROW (3)
SUMMONS AVAILABLE FOR CREATION:
INSECTS:
BEASTS:
BIRDS:
PLANTS:
STONES:
Do you realize what you're saying?
All it takes is one misstep and even
C-rank adventurers can end up dead.
Yes, which is why I want to learn
as much as I can.
Here's an idea! Let's do a little shopping first!
Hm?
Trust me, Milci! You'd grab way more attention
with a bolder wardrobe!
Right back at you, Rita.
I bet this chain mail would look stunning on you.
Aw! It's super stylish!
Yahoo! My first equipment shop!
I was just thinking about hitting one up.
What are you in the market for?
Let's see. Something that won't hinder
my range of motion.
How about this?
It's perfect!
Gimme a break. I'm a 43-year-old man.
What do you think of this?
It may look flimsy,
but it's actually very effective.
Getting new pieces of armor over time.
It's one thing I love about games!
Next up: weapons.
NAME: ALLEN
AGE:
TALENT:       SUMMONER
LEVEL:
HP:
MP:
ATTACK:
ENDURANCE:
AGILITY:
INTELLIGENCE:
LUCK:
SKILLS:
SUMMON: 4  CREATE: 4
FUSE: 4 ENHANCE: 5
EXPANSION 3 STORAGE DELETE
SKILL LEVELS
SUMMON: 4
CREATE: 4     EXP
FUSE: 4       EXP
ENHANCE: 5     EXP
SUMMONS AVAILABLE FOR CREATION:
INSECTS:
BEASTS:
BIRDS:
PLANTS:
STONES:
INVENTORY:
INSECTS F 2 COPIES E 1 COPY
BEASTS E 13 COPIES
BIRDS E 4 COPIES
My Enhance skill is up to level 5.
That basically doubles
SKILL LEVELS
SUMMON: 4
CREATE: 4
EXP
FUSE: 4
ENHANCE: 4
EXP
the buff stats of my summons.
Oh, baby!
NAME: ALLEN
AGE:
TALENT:       SUMMONER
LEVEL:
HP:
MP:
ATTACK:
ENDURANCE:
AGILITY:
INTELLIGENCE:
LUCK:
SKILLS:
SUMMON: 4  CREATE: 4
FUSE: 4 ENHANCE: 5
EXPANSION 3 STORAGE DELETE
SKILL LEVELS
SUMMON: 4
CREATE: 4     EXP
FUSE: 4       EXP
ENHANCE: 5     EXP
SUMMONS AVAILABLE FOR CREATION:
INSECTS:
BEASTS:
BIRDS:
PLANTS:
STONES:
INVENTORY:
INSECTS F 2 COPIES E 1 COPY
BEASTS E 13 COPIES
BIRDS E 4 COPIES
I just never get tired of looking at my stats!
I thrive on this stuff!
They must've found me a C-rank monster!
I'm guessing that's an orc.
My summon creatures never get tired,
but I guess even normal monsters need sleep, huh?
Well, it's a lucky break for me.
Tama squad! Sic 'em!
Nice! That did some damage!
Huh?
Keep clawing at it! Tama squad!
YOU HAVE DEFEATED 1 ORC.
YOU HAVE GAINED 1500 EXP.
Let's go!
This will make a good monster to farm
for more level ups!
And I even scored a C-rank magic stone!
It's awesome that I'm strong enough to beat
C-rank monsters without having to trap them first.
Oops. Gotta stay humble.
I still have a long ways to go.
I'm bound to get left in the dust unless I put in
100 times the effort the normies do.
Hm?
Must've found another one.
That's a C-rank armored ant. What a whopper!
Thank God there's only one.
Raven told me he almost died
from getting swarmed by these guys.
Oh crap!
Tama squad! Go!
Uh-oh! That did nothing to it!
Change of plans.
Papillon!
Scale powder!
Your magic stone is mine!
Hard as steel!
Bruh, how?! My attack stat is 438 right now!
Huh?
Crap! It woke up!
JUST DIE ALREADY, DAMMIT!
YOU HAVE DEFEATED 1 ARMORED ANT.
YOU HAVE GAINED 3000 EXP.
Whew, finally.
Let me nab that magic stone and be on my way.
Ugh, it's too damn hard!
My sword is definitely gonna shatter first!
I can't get the stupid magic stone!
NAME:
ALLEN
AGE:
SUMMONER
LEVEL:
HP:
553 +140
MP:
846+200
ATTACK:
298 +140
ENDURANCE:
298+20
AGILITY:
560+60
INTELLIGENCE:
855+40
LUCK:
560 +200
This thing gives more EXP than an orc,
SKILLS            SUMMON: 4
CREATE: 4       EXP
FUSE: 4        EXP
ENHANCE:       5 EXP
EXPANSION 3
STORAGE
DELETE
SWORD MASTERY (3)
THROW (3)
EXP:
but it's way tougher to kill.
I mean, physical attacks don't do jack against it.
SUMMONS AVAILABLE
FOR CREATION:     INSECTS: EFGH
BEASTS: EFGH
BIRDS: EFG
PLANTS: EF
STONES: E
Are you supposed to melt it
INVENTORY:       INSECTS    E     2 COPIES
BEASTS     E     14 COPIES
BIRDS     E     4 COPIES
PLANTS     E    20 COPIES
STONES
with fire magic or what?
Wait, actually,
HP:
MP:
553 +140
846+200
ATTACK:
298 +140
ENDURANCE:
298+20
AGILITY:
560+60
INTELLIGENCE:
855+40
LUCK:
560 +200
AGILITY:
INTELLIGENCE:
LUCK:
since my intelligence stat is so high...
I betcha I can cast spells.
Are you sure this is what you want?
Seems like a pretty lame reward to celebrate
your one-year manservant anniversary.
Yes! I'm very grateful for this!
What kinda weird-ass anniversary is that, anyways?
Allen, was it?
I understand you have some questions for me?
Yes, Professor!
I'll get straight to the point: can you tell
if I have the aptitude to cast spells?
Huh? You realize you don't have a talent, right?
Nobody can use magic without a talent.
No matter. We can determine the answer right away.
Just hold your hands up to this crystal ball.
If it glows, then you have the aptitude for magic.
Okay!
This should help me figure out
what kind of magic Summoners can use.
Welp, you don't have what it takes to cast spells.
Too bad.
Told you.
Seriously? Then what is my intelligence stat for?!
Dude, this blows. The Summoner class
is a total friggin' joke.
Will a cookie make you feel better?